prince4 = [
  {"question":"煎熬","Answer":"jiānáo"},
  {"question":"水溝","Answer":"shuǐgōu"},
  {"question":"不知所措","Answer":"bùzhīsuǒcuò"},
  {"question":"挨罵","Answer":"āi mà"},
  {"question":"態度","Answer":"tàidu"},
  {"question":"堅強","Answer":"jiānqiáng"},
  {"question":"手掌","Answer":"shǒuzhǎng"},
  {"question":"珍貴","Answer":"zhēnguì"},
  {"question":"變賣","Answer":"biànmài"},
  {"question":"換錢","Answer":"huànqián"},
  {"question":"瞎","Answer":"xiā"},
  {"question":"廣場","Answer":"guǎngchǎng"},
  {"question":"即使","Answer":"jíshǐ"},
  {"question":"設想","Answer":"shèxiǎng"},
  {"question":"憐惜","Answer":"liánxī"},
  {"question":"固執","Answer":"gùzhí"},
  {"question":"肩膀","Answer":"jiānbǎng"},
  {"question":"手舞足蹈","Answer":"shǒuwǔzúdǎo"},
  {"question":"抓","Answer":"zhuā"},
  {"question":"紅鶴","Answer":"hónghè"},
  {"question":"隱居","Answer":"yǐnjū"},
  {"question":"沙漠","Answer":"shāmò"},
  {"question":"未卜先知","Answer":"wèibǔxiānzhī"},
  {"question":"史平克思","Answer":"shǐpíngkèsī"},
  {"question":"既","Answer":"jì"},
  {"question":"飛翔","Answer":"fēixiáng"},
  {"question":"戶","Answer":"hù"},
  {"question":"乞丐","Answer":"qǐgài"},
  {"question":"瑟縮","Answer":"sèsuō"},
  {"question":"發抖","Answer":"fādǒu"},
  {"question":"另","Answer":"lìng"},
  {"question":"昏暗","Answer":"hūnàn"},
  {"question":"飢餓","Answer":"jīè"},
  {"question":"而","Answer":"ér"},
  {"question":"蒼白","Answer":"cāngbái"},
  {"question":"愣愣地","Answer":"lènglèng dì"},
  {"question":"人來人往","Answer":"rénlái rénwǎng"},
  {"question":"另外","Answer":"lìngwài"},
  {"question":"座","Answer":"zuò"},
  {"question":"拱橋","Answer":"gǒngqiáo"},
  {"question":"互相摟抱","Answer":"hùxiāng lǒu bào"},
  {"question":"取暖","Answer":"qǔnuǎn"},
  {"question":"金片","Answer":"jīnpiàn"},
  {"question":"剝","Answer":"bō"},
  {"question":"分","Answer":"fēn"},
  {"question":"窮","Answer":"qióng"},
  {"question":"黃金","Answer":"huáng jīn"},
  {"question":"貧窮","Answer":"pínqióng"},
  {"question":"灰暗","Answer":"huīàn"},
  {"question":"不久","Answer":"bùjiǔ"},
  {"question":"銀","Answer":"yín"}
]